mykidstime.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy - MyKidsTime

Mykidstime Limited (we) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

## Information we may collect from you

 _We may collect and process the following data about you:_

  * information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.mykidstime.com (site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Mykidstime Limited, and when you report a problem with our site;
  * if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
  * details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders; and
  * details of your visits to our site and the resources that you access.

## Legal Basis for Collecting and Processing Your Data under GDPR

Under GDPR we collect and process personal data either through active consent because you allowed us to or because we had a legitimate interest to contact you, for example, if you are an advertiser who contacts us to ask for advertising rates and we reply we may email you in the future with similar offers and services.

## IP addresses and Cookies

We may collect information about your computer for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us: to estimate our audience size and usage pattern; to store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests; to speed up your searches; and to recognise you when you return to our site.

Cookies have been used by websites for many years, but [EU law](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/LexUriServ/LexUriServ.do?uri=CELEX:32002L0058:EN:NOT) now asks us to inform you and confirm you are OK with this. If you register with us or if you continue to use our site, you agree to our use of cookies.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

Please note that some advertisers, including Google, display advertising on our website that use advertising cookies. Some of the ads you may see are targeted based on your interests or other content you have viewed online, ultimately leading to a more relevant advertising experience. This type of behavioural advertising is generally targeted towards groups of users with similar interests.

Such online advertising helps support the free content, products and services we provide to readers.

Some of the ads you see on our site are provided by other organisations that use their own cookies to track how many people have seen a particular ad, or to track how many people have seen it more than once. The companies that generate these cookies have their own privacy policies, and we have no access to read or write to these cookies.

Please see our list of verified third party advertisers below, along with a link to each individual privacy and opt out policy.

Adform                  [Privacy Policy](https://site.adform.com/privacy-center/platform-privacy/%20)

Adobe                    [Privacy Policy](https://www.adobe.com/ie/privacy/policy.html)

AppNexus             [Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy)

Celtra                     [Privacy Policy](https://www.celtra.com/privacy-policy/)

DoubleVerify        [Privacy Policy](https://www.doubleverify.com/privacy/)

Flashtalking          [Privacy Policy](https://www.flashtalking.com/privacypolicy/)

Google Inc           [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

G-skinner             [Privacy Policy](https://createjs.com/legal/privacy.html)

IAS                          [Privacy Policy](https://integralads.com/privacy-policy/)

Moat                     [Privacy Policy](https://www.moat.co.uk/privacy-statement)

Nielsen                  [Privacy Policy](http://www.nielsen.com/content/corporate/ie/en/privacy-policy.html)

OpenX                   [Privacy Policy](https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/)

Outbrain               [Privacy Policy](https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy)

Oath                      [Privacy Policy](https://policies.oath.com/in/en/oath/privacy/index.html)

Pubmatic              [Privacy Policy](https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/)

Quantcast            [Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/)

Rubicon                 [Privacy Policy](http://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/)

Sizmek                   [Privacy Policy](https://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/)

Sovrn                     [Privacy Policy](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/)

TheTradeDesk      [Privacy Policy](https://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy)

Unruly                   [Privacy Policy](https://unruly.co/privacy/)

## Where we store your personal data

Any data that we collect from you is stored within European Economic Area (“EEA”). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you consent to join our mailing list we use ActiveCampaign to send out our mailings. ActiveCampaign stores our contact list on servers in the United States.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and you cannot share it with anyone.

Unfortunately, transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Users

A user is free to access the site without providing any information to us. If you choose to leave information or comment, we will respond to you, addressing and using your information only for the purposes for which you agree. Your right to privacy will be respected at all times by us.

## Subscribers

A subscriber will be asked to provide information at the time of subscribing. Any information you provide to us will be collected fairly by us and only be used within our organisation. It will only be supplied by us to third parties either: (a) for the purposes of any competition you have entered, in which case we will first ask your permission; or (b) if we are under obligation by law to disclose it. We will never sell your email address or other personal information to third parties. Your information is collected and stored according to prevailing data protection laws and is fully GDPR compliant.

 _We use information held about you in the following ways:_

  * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, **where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes** ;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * to notify you about changes to our service.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you. If you are a new customer we will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way or you would like to see what data we hold on you please [contact us ](https://www.mykidstime.com/contact/)use the Data Request on the dropdown on our form.

## Disclosure of your information

 _We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. We may disclose your personal information to third parties:_

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if Mykidstime Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Mykidstime Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Data security

We are committed to data security and have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard any information we collect online. We use fully encrypted software.

## Child privacy

We never collect or maintain personal information on the site from those we actually know are under 16.

## Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You will consent at that time and we can only use your data if you have consented.

You can exercise your right to prevent such processing or to find out what data we hold on you by [contacting us](https://www.mykidstime.com/contact/) – please select Data Request on the dropdown on our form.

## Affiliate, Advertiser and Partner Links

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please [contact us](https://www.mykidstime.com/contact/) – use Data Request on the dropdown.
